<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Liane Yue</title>
    <link>https://lianeyue.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Liane Yue</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lianeyue.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Félécite</title>
      <link>https://lianeyue.github.io/posts/20190730-felecite/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lianeyue.github.io/posts/20190730-felecite/</guid>
      <description>This Friday, I&amp;rsquo;m taking Felecite to the DMV for the 3rd time and final time. God willing, she&amp;rsquo;ll pass her learner&amp;rsquo;s permit test and finally achieve one of her longstanding personal goals: to drive. Why the 3rd? Because the Illinois Secretary of State&amp;hellip; rather, the entire local government&amp;hellip; is a bureaucratic nightmare, and this girl also takes a million years to get ready. Why final? Because it&amp;rsquo;s my last day in Chicago, and the pesky but important last thing I need to do before I go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago</title>
      <link>https://lianeyue.github.io/posts/20190718-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lianeyue.github.io/posts/20190718-chicago/</guid>
      <description>Hey.
I&amp;rsquo;m moving at the end of the month. I&amp;rsquo;m finding a new home again.
To everyone, myself included, this was entirely unexpected. Chicago&amp;rsquo;s not a cold city (metaphorically, not literally! duh!) but it has its distances, its special rhythms that keep you at a remove. Segregate neighborhoods, secret societies, half-years spent hidden away in parka coats and underground tunnels. After two years here, the ice was just starting to thaw, and I&amp;rsquo;ll miss it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screenwriting 101</title>
      <link>https://lianeyue.github.io/posts/20190303-screenwriting-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lianeyue.github.io/posts/20190303-screenwriting-101/</guid>
      <description>I took a film class called &amp;ldquo;Screenwriting 101&amp;rdquo; at Second City this spring. The instructor was brilliant. They were great at breaking down the elements of film/TV, explaining writing room dynamics, and advising us on the &amp;ldquo;behind the scenes&amp;rdquo; business skills needed to make it. But what I was most impressed with was their patience and ability to tailor their message to everyone in the room, which was a small and super diverse microcosm of Chicago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese New Year&#39;s Resolutions</title>
      <link>https://lianeyue.github.io/posts/20190204-chinese-new-years-resolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lianeyue.github.io/posts/20190204-chinese-new-years-resolutions/</guid>
      <description>One of my calendar new year goals was to finally, finally build a personal website.
If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, I&amp;rsquo;m happy to report that it&amp;rsquo;s been checked off the list.
So, then what? Well, seeing as I had made adequate progress towards my annual resolutions by mid-January, I immediately backslid and got caught up in the all-too-escapable wave of tedium that defines modern life. Long work weeks, bingeing a Netflix show I don&amp;rsquo;t even like, a brief but gripping Stardew Valley addiction&amp;hellip; but hey!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme Demo</title>
      <link>https://lianeyue.github.io/theme-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lianeyue.github.io/theme-demo/</guid>
      <description>Style Demo h1 Heading h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading This is bold text
This is bold text
This is italic text
This is italic text
Deleted text
This is text with inline math $\sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1$ and with math blocks:
$$ \sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1 $$
w
 Block quotes are written like so.
They can span multiple paragraphs, if you like.
 Some text, and some code and then a nice plain link with title.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://lianeyue.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lianeyue.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I believe in service leadership, in creating opportunities for myself and for others, and in embracing creative chances.
Right now, I consult with Ernst &amp;amp; Young to drive technology transformation through IT strategy, architecture and infrastructure. Before that, I managed ERP and CRM deployments at GE Healthcare and Telamon. I&amp;rsquo;ve worked across the healthcare, automotive and utilities industries (to name a few) and developed skills in UI/UX, project management, and supply chain process improvement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consulting Work</title>
      <link>https://lianeyue.github.io/portfolio/engagements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lianeyue.github.io/portfolio/engagements/</guid>
      <description>← Return
As a technology transformation consultant, I have engaged across IT, Finance, and Supply Chain to drive effective design, execution and adoption of high visibility, high-impact technology enablement programs, including:
 Full lifecycle IT sourcing and transformation Digital solutions and user experience Enterprise architecture assessment and roadmap RFP and vendor evaluation Infrastructure blueprints and cloud migration factories Program and project management  Industry Lines  Healthcare Technology Automotive Talent Utilities  Engagement Experience  Digital Solutions and User Experience – Led client workshops to design and deliver &amp;ldquo;smart&amp;rdquo; functionality and dashboard interfaces for a cloud based analytics platform at an $8bn power and utilities company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Grid Services</title>
      <link>https://lianeyue.github.io/portfolio/dgs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lianeyue.github.io/portfolio/dgs/</guid>
      <description>← Return
 Digital Grid Services (DGS) is a data and analytics tool built to help a $7b company&amp;rsquo;s operations team and field technicians provide smarter, more reliable service to 3 million customers of electricity and natural gas.
Summary The DGS initiative launched in parallel to an ongoing advanced metering infrastructure (AMI) deployment, which I also project managed. Because of my interest in digital innovation, I jumped at the opportunity to interview operations leads and senior directors, write requirements, and design the new solution from scratch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illustration</title>
      <link>https://lianeyue.github.io/illustration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lianeyue.github.io/illustration/</guid>
      <description>Traditional and Fine Art. Clockwise from top left: (1) acrylic with paint markers, (2) colored and watercolor pencil, (3) Simon Birch study in oil, (4) suminagashi, and (5) oil pastels. I also work in watercolors, gouache, and orizomegami.


Digital and Illustration. I like to sketch in pen/pencil and finish with Photoshop, Illustrator or Krita.
For commissions or additional examples, feel free to shoot me an email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://lianeyue.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lianeyue.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Creative  Communication Design Painting and Illustration Creative Writing     Strategic  Enterprise Architecture Supply Chain Application Migration     Technical  Timelapse Camera Prototype Hotel Management Database Web Development    Creative and Strategic  Digital Grid Services     Technical and Creative  Product Design     Strategic and Technical  Data Modeling     All  strtchmrks Magazine</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://lianeyue.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lianeyue.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Creative  Communication Design Painting and Illustration Creative Writing     Strategic  Enterprise Architecture Supply Chain Application Migration     Technical  Timelapse Camera Prototype Hotel Management Database Web Development    Creative and Strategic  Digital Grid Services     Technical and Creative  Product Design     Strategic and Technical  Data Modeling     All  strtchmrks Magazine</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>strtchmrks Magazine</title>
      <link>https://lianeyue.github.io/portfolio/strtchmrks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lianeyue.github.io/portfolio/strtchmrks/</guid>
      <description>← Return
 strtchmrks (pronounced “stretch marks”) is a growing online community of women and non-binary folks that gathers together to find beauty in their scars and empower creative voices, even as our bodies grow and change. Monthly themes serve to encourage connection and inspire poetry, prose, and visuals for publication.
PRELIMINARY WORDMARK SKETCHES
 Summary To give direction to the project, I conducted user research, designed the brand and visuals, built and managed the website, and wrote the business plan and content strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>