<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Liane Yue</title>
    <link>https://lianeyue.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Liane Yue</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lianeyue.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Félécite</title>
      <link>https://lianeyue.github.io/posts/20190730-felecite/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lianeyue.github.io/posts/20190730-felecite/</guid>
      <description>This Friday, I&amp;rsquo;m taking Felecite to the DMV for the 3rd time and final time. God willing, she&amp;rsquo;ll pass her learner&amp;rsquo;s permit test and finally achieve one of her longstanding personal goals: to drive. Why the 3rd? Because the Illinois Secretary of State&amp;hellip; rather, the entire local government&amp;hellip; is a bureaucratic nightmare, and this girl also takes a million years to get ready. Why final? Because it&amp;rsquo;s my last day in Chicago, and the pesky but important last thing I need to do before I go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago</title>
      <link>https://lianeyue.github.io/posts/20190718-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lianeyue.github.io/posts/20190718-chicago/</guid>
      <description>Hey.
I&amp;rsquo;m moving at the end of the month. I&amp;rsquo;m finding a new home again.
To everyone, myself included, this was entirely unexpected. Chicago&amp;rsquo;s not a cold city (metaphorically, not literally! duh!) but it has its distances, its special rhythms that keep you at a remove. Segregate neighborhoods, secret societies, half-years spent hidden away in parka coats and underground tunnels. After two years here, the ice was just starting to thaw, and I&amp;rsquo;ll miss it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screenwriting 101</title>
      <link>https://lianeyue.github.io/posts/20190303-screenwriting-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lianeyue.github.io/posts/20190303-screenwriting-101/</guid>
      <description>I took a film class called &amp;ldquo;Screenwriting 101&amp;rdquo; at Second City this spring. The instructor was brilliant. They were great at breaking down the elements of film/TV, explaining writing room dynamics, and advising us on the &amp;ldquo;behind the scenes&amp;rdquo; business skills needed to make it. But what I was most impressed with was their patience and ability to tailor their message to everyone in the room, which was a small and super diverse microcosm of Chicago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese New Year&#39;s Resolutions</title>
      <link>https://lianeyue.github.io/posts/20190204-chinese-new-years-resolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lianeyue.github.io/posts/20190204-chinese-new-years-resolutions/</guid>
      <description>One of my calendar new year goals was to finally, finally build a personal website.
If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, I&amp;rsquo;m happy to report that it&amp;rsquo;s been checked off the list.
So, then what? Well, seeing as I had made adequate progress towards my annual resolutions by mid-January, I immediately backslid and got caught up in the all-too-escapable wave of tedium that defines modern life. Long work weeks, bingeing a Netflix show I don&amp;rsquo;t even like, a brief but gripping Stardew Valley addiction&amp;hellip; but hey!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>